Hi, and that's last on the evil norm how to organize your work using Chai Jippity projects
It's really game changer feature which help me organize my project much better and spend less time and in the lesson
I want to share this experience with you
This feature will help you keep everything clean and structured. So let's talk first. What is project is?
The projects in Chai Jippity is like folders for your work
Each project keeps its own chart files and some custom instructions in one place
So you can send about projects like about separate workspaces and you can use them to organize your ideas
file some ongoing chart just like you do with folders in your code editor
So let me show you some examples how I how I use for example projects in how you can use it
For example, I'm have my own my main project my work where I'm doing a very building direct application
I'm also learning react. Yeah, I'm also have my project kind of a side application where I'm building something and I also for example have my block about
AI tools. Yeah, imagine and for all of this for each of this project
I have different requirements. I use different stack for my site project and for my job project
for example, I need a different
A different type of response for when I learn in react
I want to have a detailed and really with a lot of examples
But when I write in a blog about the I tools I want to have a short because for example
I'm doing posts on Twitter or link it on Twitter for example, and I need really short messages. Yeah
And each project in charge of PT can has its own context
technical stack rules and writing style
So and I will show you now how to organize it. So let's first create all the projects the first one will be learn a react
I'll you can choose an icons for example. I choose the blue car and
This icon I create this project
Okay, let's create all the projects and then I will show you how to set up the instructions
So the another project will be a job project
Let's use the green car and the door icon
Okay, let's refresh page project disappears. Yep. It's good. Okay. The next project will be kind of a type project
Let's have it. I don't know like with the code icon and
pilot power
Yeah, and another one will be
Block about E itos AI those block. I'll let you tell them all the red one and
like this icon
So we created with you for projects and now we can set up an instructions for each of this project
for example, let's start with learn a react project and
I will click three dots here and edit. We'll click edit instructions
Oh the same as we did in the first lesson with custom instructions. You can explain what is the goal of this project
What is it for example technical style or what terms?
Uh, it's about uh, what what style or turn you want. Chi GPT will give you announced first and etc
Oh, let me copy paste. I already prepared something
So the goal of this project is practice react basics and improve my coding styles
Technical stack is the latest react version and pipe script
instructions. I want Chi GPT explain all the code really short and simple
Uh, it use bullet points and short summaries and it always show clear working code examples. I will save it
Oh
Uh, for example for EIA for job project
Let's add instructions
The job projects
I don't have a different uh, the goal is work on companies for the application
technical stack is view jazz the second version JavaScript and jazz for writing a unit test
instructions. It should follow some company coding rules
You can share some files like he has cleaned file or some I know package JSON file that it will understand all the versions
He used and it can use the right methods with library versions
Um, so this added the context. It will help you get more precise answers
You can uh, my instruction also says avoid the right and some stable code because my goal with work project not add some
mod add not having a lot of changes just
Pushing the parts I read in it. Uh, also just some small safe improvements only. Okay. I don't save it
So the next one will be the site project
For the site project. I don't use of course the latest technologies latest technical stack
So that's why it will be different and in a while you see the magic of these instructions
Now the goal is right block for sorry. It was the wrong the wrong
instructions
Uh, so for the site project is goal is build your own idea and try new technical technologies
The technical stack is a latest react the next jazz type script and we test the writing unit
instruction is used functional components and react books following some modern practices and best practices
Suggest new tool for libraries and give ready to quite be quality examples and focus on clean model solutions
so let's save it and
Now we need to also upload instructions for EI tools blog project
instructions
So any instruction is the following write blog posts and tutorials
It's the goal of this project. The technical stack is I will
I mentioned the EI assistance or EI tools
I want to talk about an instruction is X and EI experts
Explain the reader simply use some simple English words and print it on
Focus on explanation with clear examples and keep content short clear and helpful
Oh, and now let me show you all the magic
I mentioned I am learning the react and I don't know of for example how some hoop works. I can ask how we use state
works
You see it's respond really short
Yeah, it will give me the clear code examples. It uses the bullet points
And so you see like what is the use state? How to use it?
The more bigger example how it works and some bonus tip here and so
And this is the way how we work. So and you see a chart under this project
The next one is job project for the job project for example
Let me ask to create some component to see how it will write the code
Create a simple for example product
component
And write unit test
Let's say two three cases
And you see it build component on you just
I even didn't mention anything in this shot. You remember the instructions
Build me the view just template
Oh, I like it. The unit test was written on just
Using just and view test your tools. I like it. Oh, you even you shouldn't mention any time you're the converges
So now let's reach now to the site project
For example, I don't know all I'm starting building your application. I just want to have a create
Simple layout with the game form for example
Let's see how it uses the react and make yes
Let's see we have up page. We have the page. Yeah, we have the game form. We use
What we use else. Yeah, we use just a page structure
So and you don't care about um
Knowledge because our job project is on different technical stack and I just write what I want to get and it's
Remember everything and for example, let's now check how it works for AI to block like
Let me ask right
me quick
person about the I
Might be giving me one latest feature
Yeah, those
F
So let's see
Yeah, he's searching but in the web by default
Because it's kind of complex question
So one of the latest and most importantly at those introducing and compiled actions in windows this feature and force
Okay, uh my prompt wasn't clear. Maybe let's ask
Give me one
lightest
For AI too
Sorry, I like this
feature per AI too and explain it short and just explain it because I already mentioned make it short
Okay, he's doing a search in the web
Suddenly okay windows compiled to go via okay, I don't like it
Let's take the
Instructions
Which I GPT project
The instructions technical stack
Uh
Let's say Ei
tools, maybe it's not clear for him
So we can face the same problems. It's always important to
Update the context. So let's talk maybe in your chat. Give me one latest feature. Where do I do and explain it?
I think we should answer about the items we provided to him
Yeah, now here understand what is Ei tools what I mean
Now we have chai GPT
As memory updates
A lot has enhanced reasoning with those use Gemini as one to model reasoning
Grok
If Elon Musk has real-time social media integration and deep seek has video understanding so
And this way. So you shouldn't provide your like repeated instructions every time
So I hope you will use this feature often because it really simplify
your work your
Work with chai GPT and see you in the next lessons